[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a 1993 comedy/drama, Johnny Depp starred as the son of a morbidly obese woman with this last name.", "correct_answer": "Grape", "incorrect_answers": ["Appleby", "Orange", "Pearson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Diamonds\u2019 properties are commonly measured by the so called \u201cfour Cs.\u201d What do the four Cs stand for?", "correct_answer": "Carat, clarity, color, and cut", "incorrect_answers": ["Chemical balance, color, clarity and carat", "Carat, capacity, color and clarity", "Cut, calcification, carat, and cut"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vukodlak is one of the Slavonic names of which scary mythical monster?", "correct_answer": "Werewolf", "incorrect_answers": ["Dragon", "Vampire", "Ghost"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This book, which bears the printed date 11th May 868, is known as the oldest-dated printed book.", "correct_answer": "The Diamond Sutra scroll", "incorrect_answers": ["The Gutenburg Bible", "The first history of China", "The Book of the Dead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "99% of the broccoli crop in U.S.A. is produced in these two states.", "correct_answer": "California and Arizona", "incorrect_answers": ["Ohio and Maryland", "Florida and Texas", "Kansas and Nebraska"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When the Tomato Frog is threatened its skin secretes a thick substance containing a toxin.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are Mercury, Venus, Earth and Mars mostly made of?", "correct_answer": "rock", "incorrect_answers": ["gas", "none of these", "ice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the recently deceased family who finally had to realise that they were dead in the movie Beetlejuice?", "correct_answer": "Maitland", "incorrect_answers": ["Giordano", "Deitz", "Donovan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1998 Independent film was also shot in Death Valley Junction, CA.  What is the correct name of the film?", "correct_answer": "Welcome to Serendipity", "incorrect_answers": ["Tumbleweeds and Aliens", "Hot Moon", "Serendipity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is no word in the English language that rhymes with orange.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tall actress is famous for her portrayal of Ripley in the film Alien.", "correct_answer": "Sigourney Weaver", "incorrect_answers": ["Heather Graham", "Laura Dern", "Sarah Silverman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Prior to becoming a famous director, he was a member of one of the top comedy duos of the 1960s. His first big movie Whos Afraid of Virginia Woolf (1966) was followed by The Graduate (1967).", "correct_answer": "Mike Nichols", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Siegel", "Sike Jonze", "Paul Greengrass"]}]